One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Retainers of Glory
الخدم المخلصين
Sir Kin'emon! Sir Denjiro! Rear Entrance
كينيمون-دونو، دنجيرو-دونو المدخل الخلفي
Best of luck!
حظًّا طيِّبًا
To you as well!
!ولكم أيضًا
We have no money, Lord Oden!
!لا مال لدينا يا أودين-ساما
Truly?!
!ماذا؟
We have nothing to eat for supper!
!ولا عشاء لدينا لليوم
Okay, I have a job for you!
!حسنٌ، مهمتكم هي طلب الطعام من أهالي البلدة
Again?!
مجددًا؟
I am sure it was painful, everyone.
...شقَّ عليكم هذا يا رفاق
Kin...
...كين-سان
For now, let us march on.
لنواصل المضي قُدمًا حاليًا
Izo...
...إيزو
Have you made peace with perishing here?
أيلائمك أن تقضي نحبك ها هنا؟
I will not miss another chance to die.
سئمتُ النجاة من الموت عدة مرات
Then let us go.
...حسنٌ، لنتعجل
Okiku.
يا أوكيكو...
Make your choice, samurai of Orochi!
،تخيَّروا فورًا يا ساموراي أوروتشي
Do you wanna die alongside your lord Orochi here?!
أتفضلون الموت إلى جانب سيدكم أوروتشي؟
Or will you conquer the world with us?!
أم الهيمنة على العالم إلى جانبنا؟
I'm well aware of how loyal you samurai are.
أنا على علمٍ بمدى ولاء الساموراي
I admire even those of you who challenge us!
وأني لأكنّ كل الاحترام لمن يتحدانا فيكم
The 5,000 strong Oniwabanshu, the ninja force of Wano!
...حشد نينجا بلاد وانو ومعهم خمسة آلاف من الأونيابانشو
Allow us to serve you!
!جميعهم طوع أمرك...
Likewise, the samurai of Wano, 5,000 strong!
...ومن طرفنا، قوات ساموراي وانو الخمسة آلاف
Henceforth, we serve you!
!سنخدم تحت إمرتك...
Welcome aboard!
!أهلًا بكم
Shogun Orochi...
...أوروتشي-ساما
Well, that's that...
لا يهم بأيِّ حال
Good to hear! I didn't wanna turn coat and have to kill you guys outta nowhere!
ارتاح بالي، لم أرغب في أن نصبح أعداءً لكم ونقتلكم
Pleasure workin' with ya!
أتشوَّق لما هو قادم
They have no right to be called samurai!
!لا تستحقوا حتى أن يُطلق عليكم ساموراي أيها الملاعين
Hold it in for now, Boss Hyogoro!
!اضبط نفسك أيها الزعيم هيوغورو
To think you actually brought that worthless shogun's troops to our side...
،لا أصدق أنك جنّدتَ قوات شوغن بلا قيمة
You're not half bad.
يا لخباثتك
Now our forces are really coming together.
القوات منظمة بقوامةٍ الآن
Let me go!
!اتركني
No! Get off me!
كلا، كفوا عن هذا
Keep them restrained.
شدّوا وثاقهم
I'm not letting you get away with this!
!لن ندعكم تفلتون بفعلتكم
If Shinobu can escape, we still have a chance!
طالما شينوبو-تشان طليقة فالأمل قائم
I'm sorry, Onami!
عذرًا يا أونامي
I must advance!
سأسبقكم
Hurry and help Momo!
هبِّي إلى نجدة مومو-تشان فورًا
Lord Oden knew!
...أدرك أودين-ساما هذا
He knew that felling Orochi would change nothing!
،الإطاحة بأوروتشي لن تغير شيئًا
The only one in need of defeat for the past twenty years has been Kaido!
من توجب الإطاحة به منذ عشرين عامًا هو كايدو لا غيره
As it stands now, within Wano...
...بهذا غدت بلاد وانو
there's no shogun or any samurai serving him!
بلا شوغن ولا ساموراي يخدمون تحت إمرته
The unwitting citizens of the Flower Capital...
...سكان عاصمة الزهور الغافلون
must be enjoying the festivities too much to see that this will be their last day.
يحتفلون بصخبٍ شديد دون علمٍ أن هذه ليلتهم الأخيرة
Hey, brat!
!أيها الشقي
I've had my doubts for a while.
،طالما ساورني الشك
A coward like you...
جبان مثلك
can't be the son of a daredevil like Kozuki Oden!
ما كان ليكون ابن الباسل كوزكي أودين
I...
...أنا
This execution will bring about an end to the old Wano.
،الهدف من هذا الإعدام هو إرساء خاتمة للعهد القديم في بلاد وانو
Looking back on that day twenty years ago...
،وإن أسعفتني ذاكرتي لما حدث قبل عشرين سنة
inside that burning castle...
،أثناء وجودنا داخل القلعة المحترقة
you never answered my question!
!لم تجب سؤالي
Please... save me...!
!النجدة
What is your name?
ما اسمك؟
Answer!
!أجهر به
Father!
!والدي
Somebody, help me!
!لينقذني أحد
If you aren't the son of Kozuki Oden and Toki,
إلّم تكن ابنًا لكوزكي أودين وتوكي
I'll call off the execution immediately.
سأوقف الإعدام حالًا
After all, such a false accusation would tarnish my reputation.
سأعتذر منك لأنها كانت تهمة فظيعة بحقك
However, if you still insist on calling yourself their son...
،ولكن إن تمسكت بالقول إنك ابنهما
you'll face the same fate Oden did.
فستلقى نفس مصير أودين
I'll ask you one more time, brat.
!سأسألك مرة أخرى أيها الشقي
What is your name?!
ما اسمك؟
Viceroy Kaido is so generous!
!كايدو-ساما متسامح
All the rugrat has to do is lie and he gets to live!
!كل ما على ذلك الطفل فعله هو الكذب لينجو
Think up a good name, kiddo!
!أمتعنا باسم مسلٍّ يا صبي
Even if you have to lie, please choose to survive!
...لا بأس إن كذبت من أجل أن تبقى حيًّا
Lord Momonosuke!
!يا مومونوسكي-ساما...
What?! Then that boy...
...أتعني أن ذاك الصبي
is the real Kozuki Momonosuke?!
هو كوزكي مومونوسكي الحقيقي؟...
That's right!
أجل
Oden's retainers are all alive!
!كلُّ خدم أودين أحياء
What?!
!ماذا؟
Intruders!
!دخلاء
Outta my way!
!لا تعترضوا طريقي
If all the Red Scabbards samurai I saw that day are...
...إن كان جميع ساموراي الأغماد الذين رأيتهم ذلك اليوم
If they're all alive, then that's wonderful!
!إن كان جميعهم أحياء فإن هذا أمرٌ مذهل
Just wonderful!
!مذهل حقًّا
I can hardly believe it!
!لا يُصدق
Momonosuke is waiting for you!
مومونوسكي ينتظرك
Let's hurry!
لنسرع، أليسَ جميع الأغماد التسعة هنا؟
Lemme go, Yamabro!
!أنزليني يا ياماو
Yamabro? Why are you calling me that?
ياماو»؟ ما معنى هذا؟»
Please stop, Young Master Yamato!
!توقف من فضلك يا ياماتو-ساما
Stop!
!مهلًا
Young Master Yamato and Straw Hat Luffy are heading your way!
!السيد اليافع ياماتو وقبعة القش لوفي يتوجهان نحوكم
To the Performance Floor?
أتقصد طابق العرض المباشر؟
Yes! We'll catch them!
أجل، سنقبض عليهما
Don't bother.
توقفوا
You're no match–
...فأنتم لن
They dare to mess with my men?!
كيف لهما أن يعبثا برجالي؟
Yamato!
!ياماتو
You're gonna pay for this!
!لن أغفر لك
No way! Usopp, not over here!
!كلا يا أوسوب! اسلك طريقًا آخر
It looks dangerous!
!أستشعر خطرًا
You heard the broadcast earlier!
،سمعتُ البث توًّا
They're gonna kill Momo!
!سيقتلون مومو
The giants!
!العمالقة
They'll gobble us up!
،سيلتهموننا أحياء
Turn around, Usopp!
لنعد يا أوسوب
Stow your fears, Chopper!
،لا تخف يا تشوبر
We fought an Emperor to a standstill!
!فقد قاتلنا إمبراطورة على قدم المساواة
Believe in the General Franky! It was tough enough to withstand Big Mom's attacks!
!ثق بصلابة الجنرال فرانكي التي تحملت هجمات البيغ مام
I can't!
!مُحال
I can't handle these monsters!
!مُحال علينا أن نواجه تلك الوحوش
Never give up!
!لا تيأس
Never surrender!
!ولا تستسلم
Tank Commander Chopper, what are your orders?!
يا نقيب الدبابة تشوبر، ما أوامرك؟
Retreat! Retreat!
الانسحاب، آمرك بالانسحاب
Are you scared?!
!أخائفٌ أنت؟
Cut the "samurai" crap!
!أيُّ مُحاربٍ أنت؟
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates someday!
!أنا من سيصير ملك القراصنة يومًا
Because your father is a great man...
،لأنّ والدك رجلٌ عظيم
and you will one day carry this nation on your shoulders.
وأنت من سيحكم هذه البلاد يومًا
The meaning of your name?
معنى اسمك؟
Yes!
أجل
I want you to grow into a compassionate, open-minded, and admirable man.
...أردت لك أن تكون رجلًا رقيق الفؤاد واسع الأفق جدير بالإعجاب
Momo!
!«مومو»...
Momo...
...«إن «مومو
means peerless!
!«يعني «من لا مثيل له
My name is...
...إن اسمي
Kozuki Momonosuke!
!كوزكي مومونوسكي
One day, I will become...
...وإن منصب الشوغن في بلاد وانو
the shogun of Wano!
!لن يتقلده رجل غيري...
Lord Momonosuke!
!مومونوسكي-ساما
I swear I will save you no matter the cost, Lord Momonosuke!
!سأنقذك حتمًا يا مومونوسكي-ساما
Well said, Momonosuke!
!أحسنت القول يا مومونوسكي
We're almost there, Luffy!
كدنا نصل يا لوفي
Let me take these off!
،سأنزعهما عنك
I promised you!
!كما وعدتك
If you would!
من فضلك
However, just to be safe...
...احتياطًا... ارمهما بعيدًا
Although, I doubt they'll explode...
وإن كنت أشك في أنها ستنفجر
Is Wano filled with only halfwits?!
!ألا تنجب بلاد وانو سوى الحمقى؟
Father... Mother...
...والدي... أمي
I merely wished to be a man...
...كل ما أردته هو
who would be free of shame when next he sees you in the afterlife.
!ألَّا ألطخ اسميكما بالعار لأكون رجلًا تفخران بلقياه في العالم الآخر...
Hiyori, I wish I could see you again, even if for a moment...
...يا هيوري، وددت لو رأيتُكِ مجدّدًا ولو للحظة
I do not want to die!
لا أريد الموت
I do not want to cry!
لا أريد البكاء
A samurai should not cry in front of others...
...ما كان للمحارب أن يبكي أمام الناس
How shameful...
!هذا مخزٍ
They came off!
!نُزعا
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
!ساخن، ساخن، ساخن، ساخن
Luffy?!
!لوفي
Dammit!
!سحقًا
That freaking cowrilla!
!ذلك الغوريلا اللعين
He was going to kill me!
!كان ينوي قتلي
What was that explosion?!
ما هذا الانفجار؟
Go find out, pronto!
تفقدوا أمره
Now it's clear to me.
،فهمت أخيرًا
That man is no longer my father!
إنه ليس بأبٍ لي بعد الآن
Was this your doing, you spoiled brat?!
أكنت المتسبب في هذا أيها الابن الأحمق؟
Hold on, Yamabro!
!مهلًا يا ياماو
You stupid old man!
!أيها الأب اللعين
We made it just in time...
...وصلنا في الوقت المناسب
but it's not gonna be me or Yamabro.
...ولكن لا يجدر بي أو بك التقدم يا ياماو
We're not the ones who'll start this battle!
!لسنا من سيدقّ أجراس هذه المعركة
The Red Scabbards!
!ساموراي الأغماد
Where did they come from?!
من أين أتوا؟
The rulers of the minks?!
!ملوك المينك؟! إنهم أحياء
You damn ghosts! Prepare for my counterattack!
أيتها الأشباح اللعينة، سأرد لكم فعلتكم
Izo!
!إيزو
Hey, dumbasses!
!أيها الأوغاد
Quit drinking already!
!كفاكم احتساء الشراب
Go grab your weapons!
!اقبضوا أسلحتكم
It's a raid!
!هذه غارة
Are you...
!أنت كيوشيرو؟
Kaido!
!كايدو
You half-ghost bastards!
!لستم سوى أشباح أيها الأوغاد
Surrender Name And Thoughts...
!تخلَّوا عن أسمائكم
Calm all Hesitation!
!وتخلَّوا عن حكمتكم
Your blades...
!سيوفكم الوضيعة... لن تجرحني
Stake your lives on this blow!
!راهِنوا بحياتكم على هذه الضربة
Oden!
!أودين
Never set foot in Wano again!
!إيّاك والعودة إلى بلاد وانو
SNATCH!
سوناتشي
Oden Two-Sword Style:
تو
Halcyon Totsuka!
توغين
The scar Oden left me with...
...الندبة التي خلفها بي أودين
Why does it hurt?
لمَ تؤلمني؟
How do these blades pierce my body?!
كيف لأنصالهم أن تخترق بدني؟
Do not underestimate my samurai!
!لا تستخف بأتباعي السّاموراي
They can forget me...
...لا أمانع
for all I care...
!أن أُنسى
but...
...لكن
my spirit will live on!
!ستعيش روحي
Are they using Oden's ryuo?!
!أيستعملون ريو أودين؟
Pierce through!
!اطعنوه
They really are Oden's retainers!
!خدم أودين الحقيقيون
They sure are strong!
!إنهم أقوياء
Quite the deadly banquet!
!يا لخطورة هذه المأدبة
Did Kaido kick the bucket?
هل هلك كايدو؟
Fight back!
!قاتلوا واقتلوا أولئك الأغماد
So Straw Hat, Kid, and all the others were merely distractions for this ambush?!
أكان قبعة القش وكيد ومن معهما تمويهًا لهذا الهجوم المفاجئ؟
Stay alert, you guys!
توخوا الحذر يا رفاق
There could still be intruders around here!
يحتمل وجود دخلاء آخرين
Spot on!
أصبت
Open your ears, weaklings!
انصتوا أيها الجبناء
We won't let you bring harm to Kin'emon and his samurai!
لن يطال أذاكم جماعة كينيمون
Alright! Let's get in on this!
حسنٌ، لننضم لهم
We'll give Kaido another beating!
!لنَنَل من كايدو ثانيةً
There you are!
!عثرت عليك
Yamato!
!يا ياماتو
Headbutt!
!الناطحة
Ulti!
!أولتي
The nerve, striking me as you did!
كيف تجرؤ على ضربي مبكرًا؟
I am on your side, yet you brutally assaulted me,
،هاجمت حليفتك
and now you're running around the place with that Straw Hat...
،تركض رفقة قبعة القش في كل مكان
Whatever are you doing?!
!ماذا حل بك-أرينسو؟
Nothing to get upset over.
،كل هذا مقبول
The day that I become Kozuki Oden is finally here!
!أتى اليوم الذي أكون فيه كوزكي أودين أخيرًا
What are you talking about?! Are you crazy?!
لا أفهمك، أفقدت رشدك؟
Young Master Yamato, we have a problem!
حلَّت علينا مصيبة أيها السيد اليافع ياماتو
Your father was just attacked,
هوجم أبيك توًّا وتسلل أعداءٌ إلى الطابق
Please stop fooling around!
!كفاك حماقةً
I'm well aware!
أعرف
I'm not your ally anymore, and I don't give a damn if my father dies!
أنا لست حليفًا لكم بعد الآن، ولا يعنيني موت أبي
– What?!
!ماذا؟
What is it this time?
ما هذه الضوضاء؟
This banquet is getting far too rowdy...
هذه المأدبة عامرة بالأحداث حقًّا
Gum-Gum...
فاكهة المطاط
Elephant Gun!
مسدس الفيل
That boy...
...إن هذا
Oh crap!
!مصيبة
She saw Luffy!
!انتبهت للوفي
Big Mom!
!بيغ مام
But I'm busy right now!
!أنا مشغول حاليًا
I finally found you...
...عثرتُ عليك أخيرًا
Straw Hat!
!يا قبعة القش...
Mortar!
المسدس
Carrot! Let's make a break for it!
!لنهرب يا كاروت
Got it!
نعم
Better get ready!
انتبه لما هو آتٍ
Black Ball!
الكرة السوداء
Hey, are you okay?!
مهلًا، هل أنت بخير؟
Here goes!
ها أنا ذي
Same here!
وأنا أيضًا
Thundercloud Rod!
عصا غيوم الرعد
Eleclaw!
مخلب الكهرباء
Ninpo: Ectoplasm Thunder!
فنون النينجا
We did it!
مرحى
You came into my territory and disgraced my crew!
،من أجل أن أقتلك جَزاء إهانتك لقراصنتي
So I came all the way from Totto Land to kill you!
...شقيت طريقي من توتولاند لأبطش بك
Straw Hat!
!يا قبعة القش
Why are you here?
لمَ أتيت هنا؟
And don't tell me it's to take down Kaido, because that'd be too damn rich.
لا يعقل أن تكون غايتك الإطاحة بكايدو فإن ذلك سخيفٌ حقًّا
It's not that!
كلا، ليست تلك غايتي
Luffy?!
!لوفي
What do you mean, Sir Straw Hat?!
ما الخطب يا فتى قبعة القش؟
It's not, Luffy?!
ألم تُرِد ذلك يا لوفي؟
No!
...كلا
I'm...
...أنا
After twenty years,
«سيأتي ساموراي الأغماد بعد عشرين عامًا ليأخذوا بثأرهم»
Nobody believed Orochi's delusions, but it would seem they're coming to pass.
أضغاث أحلام أوروتشي التي لم يصدقها أحد بدأت تترابط بمنطقية
I can't believe you made common cause with pirates.
من قد يتخيل أنكم تحالفتم مع قراصنة
The rumor about the shadows at the ruins of Oden Castle...
،إشاعات الأشباح التي تجوب أطلال قلعة أودين
Punk Hazard.
،بانك هازارد
Dressrosa.
،دريسروزا
The phantom island Zou.
،الجزيرة الوهمية زو
And the crew behind it all, the Straw Hat Pirates!
!وكلها كان وراءها طاقم قبعة القش
By some curious coincidence,
،وما صبَّ في مصلحتكم
you people were hiding in the shadows of my enemies, the Straw Hats.
أن محطّ تركيزي كان قبعة القش الذي اتخذتموه ساترًا لكم
Some of you held out for twenty years, while others jumped ahead and ran about,
،تحامل بعضكم عشرين سنة
and just like that, your troops were gathered.
وعددتم العدة والجُند
But pirates will stab you in the back!
،ولكن القراصنة سيغدرون بكم
The moment they sense defeat, they'll abandon you and run.
سيتخلون عنكم حين تكاد خسارتهم ويولون هاربين
I've already taken Straw Hat Luffy out once!
كما أني سبق وكسرت شوكة قبعة القش سلفًا
You slander the man!
كلامك فيه إهانة له
Sir Luffy and your band could not be more different!
لوفي-دونو مختلف عنكم جميعًا
You, Kaido, the officers, Orochi, and every last person under them!
أنتِ، وكايدو وقادته، وأوروتشي وأتباعه
I'm here to kick all your asses!
!لأبطش بكم أجمعين
He is the man who will stand at the pinnacle of the sea someday!
،إنه الرجل الذي سيتسيد البحار يومًا
Even if we die, he shall live on!
،سيواصل القتال وإن لقينا حتفنا
Wano will see daybreak once more!
وليبزغن الفجر على بلاد وانو حتمًا
Because...
...فهذا
such was the promise we made to our lord!
!وعد قطعناه لسيدنا...
It's gonna be an all-out war!
!إنها حربٌ شاملة
Don't push your luck.
لا تغتر بنفسك
You only have a few hundred troops!
فلا يقاتل معك سوى بضعة مئات
She's right, numbskulls.
فعلًا، يا لحماقتكم
What?
ماذا هنالك؟
It's an emergency!
!حالة طارئة
Thousands of intruders are entering from the rear!
آلاف الدخلاء يقتحمون المكان من المدخل الخلفي
How's that possible?!
!كيف يعقل هذا؟
Fine!
لا بأس، إن كانت هذه رغبتكم
I'll cut you up as much as you like.
سأقطعكم كما تشاؤون
Screw you!
لا تعبث معنا
Exactly...
أجل، أنتم في ورطة
But why...?!
لماذا؟
A samurai...
...ساموراي
Sir Zorojuro! We are by your side!
زوروجورو-دونو، سنمد لك يد العون
This is Point C!
،«هنا النقطة «ج
It's all the samurai we caught in the Flower Capital...
...الساموراي الذين قبضنا عليهم في عاصمة الزهور
and the prisoners from Udon!
!وسُجناء أودون أيضًا
Punk...
وتر الغيتار الممغنط
Don't fall behind, boys!
أيها الرجال، لا تتكاسلوا
Thank you for clearing the way for us this far.
نشعر بالامتنان لك على إخلاء الطريق أمامنا
Keep your thanks.
لا تفهموا الأمر خاطئًا
I'm only here to take Kaido's head.
أنا هنا لنيل رأس كايدو فحسب
Get in my way, and I'll take yours too.
إن اعترضتموني فلن تسلموا مني
Appreciate the warning.
شكرًا لتحذيرك
Room!
الغرفة روم
Go to hell!
!اهلكوا
Amputate!
البتر أمبيوتيتو
Shambles!
الفوضى
The pirates that Sir Kin'emon brought...
...إن القراصنة الذين أحضرهم كينيمون
are pretty damn strong!
يُعتمد عليهم...
How did this all happen?!
!ما بال هذا الوضع؟
A former Warlord, Law, has arrived as well.
وصل الشيتشيبوكاي السابق لاو أيضًا
They're all working together and gaining power!
جميعهم متحدون معًا وأعدادهم في تزايد
Say what?!
!ماذا؟
Your Awesomeness!
!كوين-ساما
There's more?!
!أهنالك أكثر؟
At the entrance of the island,
،ثمة شأن لا نفهمه عند المدخل
Marco the Phoenix and Perospero are working together–
!يقاتل العنقاء ماركو وبيروسبيرو جنبًا إلى جنب
Hey! What happened?!
ماذا حدث؟
Hello?!
!مهلًا
Candy Maiden!
عذراء الحلوى
What's going on?!
ما الذي يجري؟
Why are they teaming up?!
لمَ يقاتل ذلكما الاثنان معًا؟
And now begins the ogre extermination.
وهكذا تبدأ عملية إبادة الغول-يوي
I'll turn every last lickety-one of the Beast Pirates into candy men.
«سأحوّل جميع أفراد طاقم قراصنة الوحوش إلى «رجال حلوى
Attention, drunkards of Onigashima!
إلى جميع السكارى في أونيغاشيما
Tonight's banquet is canceled!
مأدبة الليلة أُلغيت
Go grab your weapons!
!اقبضوا أسلحتكم
It's an enemy raid!
!الأعداء ينقضون علينا
Everyone...
...جميعكم
Kaido may be gone, but there are still three Superstars present.
لا يزال النجوم البارزون الثلاثة هنا رغم رحيل كايدو
I'm sure there will be a chance!
ولكن الفرصة ستسنح لي
Lord Momonosuke!
!يا مومونوسكي-ساما، تحامل على نفسك قليلًا بعد
Let's do this!
لنمضِ
We will take back Wano!
لنحرر بلاد وانو
I heard that, Straw Hat!
سمعتك يا قبعة القش
You say you'll kick my ass?
هل ستبطش بي أنا؟
Then go ahead and try!
!امضِ وجرّب ذلك فإني أقبل تحديك
I'll show you the world's greatest army!
!لأرينّك أعظم قوة في العالم
Sir Luffy!
!لوفي-دونو
Many thanks!
!أشكرك جزيل الشكر
Kin'emon! I'll catch up later!
!سأوافيك لاحقًا يا كينيمون
Kaido...
...كايدو-سان
I've completely sobered up.
صحوت من ثمالتي
If it's a fight to the death you want, it's best out in the open.
إن أردتم خوض قتال حتى الموت فيُفضل خوضه في العراء
Just like that day...
،قتال أشبه بذلك اليوم
But unlike that day, Oden's already dead.
الاختلاف الوحيد هو أن أودين ميت
There's one more difference from that day.
بل ثمة اختلاف آخر عن ذلك اليوم
We deduced that when you turn into a dragon,
،توقعنا أنك إن أردت القتال بهيئة التنين
you wouldn't be able to fight in the dome.
فلن تتمكن من القتال داخل القبة
You can't understand how I've longed for this day!
لكم كنتُ أتطلع شوقًا إلى هذا اليوم
You will know our rage when we beat it into you!
سنجعلك تدرك مدى حنقنا بأقسى طريقة ممكنة
The minks...
...عشيرة المينك
We brought the warriors from our kingdom.
أحضرنا جنود مملكتنا
A flurry of snow in the clear sky...
يتساقط الثلج كَبَتلاتِ الزهور
Perfect for watching the full moon.
والبدر ساطعٌ رؤيته واضحة